Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Rose, Flora; Warburton, Clark; Nye, Claribel; Pfund, Marion C.; Papish, Jacob; Farrand, Livingston; Simons, Lloyd R.; New York State College of Home Economics.
  - Hotel Administration., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Meek, Howard B.; Betten, Cornelius; McKowne, Frank A.; American Hotel Association; Cornell University, Dept. of Hotel Administration.
  - Architecture., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Young, George; Cornell University College of Architecture; Regional development.
  - Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Engineering., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Kimball, Dexter; Cornell University College of Engineering; Federal Housing Administration.
  - Music Department., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Coffin, Foster M.; Abbott, Robert D.; Cornell University, Alumni Association; Cornell Club of Southern California.
  - Committee on Care of Campus Trees., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Massey, Louis M.; Van Blarcom, Conant; Wyman, Donald; Cornell University, Dept. of Buildings and Grounds; Dutch Elm Disease.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Eastman, Perley M.; Birdsall, Webster J.; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.; Poletti, Charles; White, Charles R.; Johnston, John; New York State Agricultural Society; Farm families.
  - American Agriculturist., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Eastman, Edward R.; Osborne, Lithgow; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.; Babcock, Howard E.; Freestone, Fred J.; Warren, George F.; Sexauer, Fred H.; Foster, Earl S.; Dean, Daniel; Cosline, Hugh L.; Association of New York State Master Farmers.
  - American Association of Agricultural College Editors., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Adams, Bristow; Kirkwood, William P.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Howard E. Babcock., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Lippman, Walter; Gannett, Frank E.; Fearon, George R.; Sibley, Harper; Grange League Federation; Agricultural policy.
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Boy Scouts of Ithaca., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Harrison, Ralph A.; Phillips, Elmer S.; Underwood, E. Victor; Stutz, Harry; Boy Scouts of Ithaca.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Committee for the Nation., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Rumely, Edward A.; Thomas, Elmer; Committee for the Nation; Economic policy; Monetary reform.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., . 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Sexauer, Fred H.; Ten Eyck, Peter G.; Brown, Edward F.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; New York State Division of Milk Control; New York Milkshed; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Milk Research Council, Inc.; Milk marketing; Cooperative marketing; Scholarships.
  - Danforth Foundation., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Danforth, William H.; Knapp, Merrill N.; Danforth Foundation.
  - Dartington Hall, Leonard K. Elmhirst., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Mott, John L.; Currie, John R.; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Dartington Hall; International Conference of Agricultural Economists; Monetary reform.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Empire State Potato Club., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Porter, Roy A.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Forward, Hervey D.; Borah, William E.; Potato industry.
  - Empire State Gas and Electric Association., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Chapin, Charles H.B.; Burritt, Maurice C.; Nixon, Maurice W.; Jennings, Burton A.; New York State Public Service Commission; New York Farm Electrification Council; Farm Gas and Electric Research Committee; Rural electrification.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    O'Neal, Edward A.; Foster, Earl S.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Smith, Ruby G.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; American Farm Bureau Federation; New York State Farm Bureau Federation.
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Foster, Earl S.; Gray, Chester H.; White, Charles R.; Osborne, Lithgow; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; New York State Dept. of Conservation; Forestry; Land acquisition; Wildlife conservation.
  - Federal Land Bank of Springfield., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Thomson, Edward H.; Myers, William I.; Ober, Hazen R.; Harriott, John F.; Hart, Van B.; Garwood, Sterling M.; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; Farm Credit Administration; Production Credit Corps; Production Credit Corporation of Springfield; Federal Housing Administration; National Farm Loan Associations; Farm mortgages; Credit unions.
  - Gannett Newspapers., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Gannett, Frank E.; Stamp, Josiah; Babcock, Howard E.; Pearson, Frank A.; Warren, George F.; Atwood, Millard V.; Skeffington, Leo B.; Committee for the Nation; Monetary reform.
  - New York State Grange., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Stanley, Harold M.; Freestone, Fred J.; Gardner, Charles M.; Eastman, Edward R.; Osborne, Lithgow; New York State Grange; New York State Dept. of Conservation; Wildlife conservation; Land acquisition.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - New York State Home Bureau Federation., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Young, Eliza K.; Capper, Arthur; MacDonald, Elizabeth; Lehman, Herbert H.; New York State Home Bureau Federation; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations; Women in agriculture.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - J Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1935-35 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Farrell, Francis D.; Gray, Lewis C.; Mumford, Herbert W.; Walton, Thomas O.; Bankhead, John H.; Cooper, Thomas P.; Coffey, Walter C.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; National Grange; American Farm Bureau Federation; American Bankers Association; Farm Credit Administration.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - N Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - New York Herald Tribune., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Roosevelt, Eleanor; Meloney, Marie M.; New York Herald Tribune Forum.
  - O Miscellaneous., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Post Standard., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    Barnum, Jerome D.; Syracuse Post Standard; New York State Rural Rehabilitation Corporation; States rights.
  - R Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Rockefeller Foundation., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    Hanson, Frank B.; May, Stacy; Warren, George F.; Aizsilnieks, A.P.; Emerson, Rollins A.; Rockefeller Foundation; Agricultural research.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - New York State College of Forestry, Samuel N. Spring., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.; Orvis, Paul B.; Spring, Samuel N.; New York Forestry and Park Association.
  - State Schools of Agriculture., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    Smith, Harlond L.; Knapp, Halsey B.; Wood, Herbert C.; Crittenden, Lee W.; Norwood, J. Nelson.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Dutch Elm Disease., 1933-35 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Van Blarcom, Conant; Massey, Louis M.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; Treman, Robert H.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Lipman, Jacob G.; Hosmer, Ralph S.; White, J. DuPratt; Herrick, Glenn W.; Architectural Advisory Board; Dutch Elm Disease.
  - Farm Debt Conciliation Committee., 1933-35 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Anderson, Alvin T.; Flansburgh, Earl A.; Myers, William I.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Hapkins, Harry L.; New York State Farm Debt Conciliation Committee; Farm Credit Administration; Federal Emergency Relief Administration; Farm mortgages; Rural electrification; Extension work; Child care.
  - Land Use and Regional Planning Board Material., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    LaMont, Thomas E.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Catherwood, Martin P.; Mann, Albert R.; Acker, Ernest R.; New York State Planning Council; New York State Public Service Commission; National Resources Planning Board; Rural electrification; Land use.
  - Rural Electrification, Committee on Research., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    Nixon, Maurice W.; Wigsten, F. Murray; Blandy, D.E.; Chapin, Charles H.B.; Farm Electrification Council; New York State Public Service Commission; Rural electrification.
  - Requests for Research., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    Bullock, C. Kenneth; Palmer, Ralph G.; Page, Henry L.; Agricultural research; Rural electrification; Pest control.
  - Temporary Emergency Relief Administration., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    Georgia, Willard E.; Daniels, Frederick I.; Carpenter, Carlos C.; Jackson, Glenn E.; Kelsey, Lincoln D.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Farm Credit Administration; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Farm mortgages.
  - Temporary Emergency Relief Administration., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    Georgia, Willard E.; Goodier, James H.; Davis, Chester C.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Birdsall, Webster J.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; New York State Rural Rehabilitation Corporation; Farm families; Extension work.
  - Monroe County Emergency Work Bureau., 1932-35 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    Bonner, J. Franklin; Carroll, F.H.; Goodman, Alpheus M.; Reconstruction Finance Corporation; Subsistence homestead projects.
  - Tompkins County Planning Project, Temporary Emergency Relief Administration., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    Hesley, Karl D.; Carpenter, Carlos C.; Jackson, Glenn E.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Land purchases; Public health; Rural electrification; Flood control.
  - Rural Advisory Committee, Temporary Emergency Relief Administration., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    Jackson, Glenn E.; Smith, Ruby G.; Freestone, Fred J.; Georgia, Willard E.; Daniels, Frederick I.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Home economics; Rural Rehabilitation Program; Public welfare.
  - Governor of the State of New York, Herbert H. Lehman., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Poletti, Charles; Canavan, Joseph J.; Mahoney, James J.
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Ten Eyck, Peter G.; Baldwin, Charles H.; New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets; Milk marketing; Agricultural legislation.
  - New York State Budget Director., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Weber, Abraham S.; New York State Division of the Budget; Agricultural marketing.
  - New York State Dept. of Conservation., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Osborne, Lithgow; New York State Dept. of Conservation; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Arnot Forest; Cayuga Lake; Conservation.
  - New York State Comptroller, Pension Commission., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Curtis, Helen; Rose, Flora; Hart, Van B.; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State Commission on Pensions; Pensions.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Harlan, Harlan H.; Simpson, Alfred D.; Johnston, John; Flick, Alexander C.; New York State Dept. of Education; New York State College of Agriculture; Agricultural legislation; Agricultural research; Budgets; Pest control; Vegetable crops.
  - New York State Dept. of Public Service., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Burritt, Maurice C.; New York State Dept. of Public Service; Rural electrification.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Howe, Frederick B.; Knight, Henry G.; Murphy, Donald R.; Morrison, Frank B.; McPhee, Hugh C.; Wallace, Henry A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Rural electrification; Agricultural education.
  - Agricultural Adjustment Administration., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Southwick, B.G.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Englund, Eric; Jardine, James T.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Agricultural research.
  - Agricultural Adjustment Administration, Land Policy Section., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Alien, Arthur A.; Southwick, B.G.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Land acquisition.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Jardine, James T.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    McCall, M.A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry; Agricultural research.
  - Soil Erosion Service., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Howe, F.B.; United States Dept. of the Interior, Soil Erosion Service; Soil Conservation.
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Myers, William I.; Farm Credit Administration; Farm mortgages; Cooperative banking; Agricultural credit.
  - United States Forest Service., 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Myers, William I.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Butler, Ovid; Pack, Charles Lathrop; Wallace, Henry A.; Ickes, Harold L.; Graves, Henry S.; United States Forest Service; American Forestry Association; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Society of American Foresters; Forestry.
  - United States Weather Bureau., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Fisher, John C.; United States Weather Bureau.
  - Governor's Agricultural Advisory Commission., 1929-33 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission; New York State College of Agriculture; Dutch Elm Disease; Agricultural education; Land use; Highways.
  - Governor's Agricultural Advisory Commission., 1929-34 (Box 8, Folder 19-20)
    Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission; Rural education; Highways; Agricultural economics; Agricultural research.
  - Memoranda on the New York State Colleges at Cornell., 1932 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    New York State College of Home Economics; New York State College of Agriculture; New York State School of Hotel Administration.
  - Reports, State Institutions at Cornell., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Englehart, Fred; New York State College of Agriculture; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; Campus buildings.
  - Reports, State Institutions at Cornell., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Alien, E.W.; Ashbaugh, E.T.; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State College of Agriculture; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; Agricultural research; Extension work.
  - Reports, State Institutions at Cornell., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Perine, E.T.; Lord, Edward; Updegraff, Harlan; New York State College of Agriculture; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - President's Office., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Farrand, Livingston; Guterman, Carl E.F.; New York State College of Agriculture; Bailey Hortorium.
  - Provost's Office., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Mann, Albert R.; New York State College of Agriculture; Agricultural research.
  - University Attorney., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Simmons, L.N.; Office of the Comptroller.
  - University Comptroller., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Bostwick, C.D.; Cornell University, Office of the Comptroller; Land acquisition.
  - University Treasurer., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Rogalsky, George F.; Columbia Broadcasting System; Rural electrification; Research funds.
  - Assistant Treasurer., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Wheeler, Ralph H.; Lloyd Preserve; Bailey Hall.
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Van Blarcom, Conant; Bailey Hall; Roberts Hall; New York State College of Agriculture, Arboretum.
  - Office of the Dean., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Farrand, Livingston; Simmons, L.N.; Cornell University, Office of the Dean.
  - Requisitions., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Work Orders., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Circular Letters., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Expense Accounts and Travel Slips., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Budget Recommendations for 1936-37., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Betten, Cornelius; Thompson, Homer C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry; New York State College of Home Economics; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - Business Office., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    New York State College of Agriculture; Fellowships; Federal funds.
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Warren, George F.; Spencer, Leland; Pearson, Frank A.; Harper, Floyd A.; Bond, Maurice C.; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; Agricultural research; Research funding; Dairy industry; Farm labor.
  - Dept. of Agricultural Economics., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Goodman, Alpheus M.; Riley, Howard W.; Robb, Byron B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering; Alaska Rural Rehabilitation Corporation; Agricultural research.
  - Agronomy., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Lyon, T.L.; Baron, John; Chandler, Robert F.; Johnstone-Wallace, Denis B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy; Soil conservation; Soil management; Agricultural research.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    Morrison, Frank B.; Savage, E.S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; Dairy industry; Milk marketing; Artificial breeding.
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Bailey, Ethel Zoe; MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Bailey Hortorium.
  - Botany., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    Reddick, Donald; Betten, Cornelius; Randolph, Lowell F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; Agricultural research.
  - Dairy Industry., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    Sherman, James M.; Sharp, Paul F.; Rossi, H. E.; Guthrie, E. S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Dairy Industry; Milk marketing.
  - Entomology., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    Matheson, Robert; Palm, Charles E.; Johannsen, O.A.; Needham, James G.; Betten, Cornelius; Bradley, J. Chester; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station; International Congress of Entomology; International Congress of Zoology; Limnology.
  - Entomology, Ornithology., 1935-36 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    Alien, Arthur A.; Sutton, George; Wright, Albert Hazen; Bump, Gardiner; New York State Dept. of Conservation; New York State College of Agriculture, Laboratory of Ornithology; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; Game management; Conservation.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Pauling, Linus; Hucker, G.J.; Wellington, Richard; Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Sayer, Charles, B.; Hamilton, J.M.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Agricultural research.
  - Office of the Director., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; National Rural Youth Committee; Soil conservation.
  - Office of the Director., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Rural electrification.
  - State Leaders Office, Farm Bureau., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Flansburgh, Earl A.; Pest control.
  - State Leaders Office, Home Bureau., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Simons, Lloyd R.
  - State Leaders Office, Junior Extension., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Wright, William T.
  - Montgomery Robinson Robinson, Montgomery E., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Charles A. Taylor., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Taylor, Charles A.; Simons, Lloyd R.
  - Farm Practice., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    King, Asa C.
  - G.A. Everett, G.E. Peabody., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Peabody, G. Eric.
  - Office of Publications., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    White, E.A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.
  - Forestry., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.; Civilian Conservation Corps; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept of Forestry; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Library., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Plant Breeding., 1936 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Emerson, Rollins A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding.
  - Plant Pathology., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Massey, Louis M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Pathology.
  - Pomology., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Heinicke, Arthur J.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Pomology.
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Hutt, Frederick B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Resident Instruction., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Betten, Cornelius; Smith, O.W.; Cornell University, Office of Resident Instruction.
  - Rural Social Organization., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Sanderson, Dwight; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Social Organization.
  - Rural Education., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Butterworth, Julian E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Education.
  - Vegetable Crops., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops.
  - Hotel., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Meek, Howard B.; Cornell University, Dept. of Hotel Administration.
  - College of Home Economics., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Rose, Flora; New York State College of Home Economics.
  - Arts and Sciences., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences.
  - Chemistry., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Cornell University, Dept. of Chemistry.
  - Engineering., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Cornell University College of Engineering.
  - Music Department., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Weaver, Paul J.; Cornell University, Dept. of Music.
  - Miscellaneous Committees., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Association., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Comellian Council., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Palmer, Archie.
  - Cornell Countryman., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Summer Session., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Men for Positions., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Farm and Home Week., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Roosevelt, Eleanor; Lehman, Herbert H.; Farm and Home Week.
  - Requests for Research., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Dutch Elm Disease., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Regional Markets., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Land Bank Appraisers Conference., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Potato Program for New York., 1935-36 (Box 9, Folder 40)